William R. Cotter Papers
© 2005 University of Connecticut
- Series II: Executive Records, 1971-1981
  - Commerce
    - Economic Development Administration (Box 54:, Folder 1166)
      - CRCOG Metro Planning Grant Application, 1979
    - Federal Maritime Administration, 1979 (Box 54:, Folder 1167)
    - Economic Development Administration, 1979 (Box 54:, Folder 1168)
  - Community Services Administration
    - General, 1979 (Box 54:, Folder 1169)
    - Fuel Assistance Program, 1979 (Box 54:, Folder 1170)
  - Consumer Product Safety Commission, 1979 (Box 54:, Folder 1171)
  - Defense
    - U.S. Marine Corps, 1979 (Box 54:, Folder 1172)
    - Air Force, 1979 (Box 54:, Folder 1173)
    - Navy, 1979 (Box 54:, Folder 1174)
    - Army, 1979 (Box 54:, Folder 1175)
  - Department of Energy, 1979 (Box 54:, Folder 1176)
  - Environmental Protection Agency (EPA), 1979 (Box 54:, Folder 1177)
  - Office of the President
    - Office of Management & Budget, 1979 (Box 54:, Folder 1178)
    - Wage and Price Council, 1979 (Box 54:, Folder 1179)
  - Federal Reserve Board, 1979 (Box 54:, Folder 1180)
  - Federal Communications Commission (FCC)
    - Religious Broadcasting, 1979 (Box 54:, Folder 1181)
  - General Accounting Office (GAO), 1979 (Box 54:, Folder 1182)
  - Federal Trade Commission, 1979 (Box 54:, Folder 1183)
  - General Services Administration, 1979 (Box 54:, Folder 1184)
  - Health, Education and Welfare (HEW)
    - General, 1979 (Box 54:, Folder 1185)
    - Education: W. Hartford Eligibility, 1979 (Box 54:, Folder 1186)
    - Welfare, 1979 (Box 54:, Folder 1187)
    - Health, 1979 (Box 54:, Folder 1188)
    - Education, 1979 (Box 54:, Folder 1189)
    - Elderly Nutrition “Meals on Wheels”, 1979 (Box 54:, Folder 1190)
    - Food and Drug Administration, 1979 (Box 54:, Folder 1191)
    - Social Security Administration, 1979 (Box 54:, Folder 1192)
  - Housing and Urban Development
    - Community Development Block Grants, 1979 (Box 54:, Folder 1193)
    - Flood Insurance Program, 1979 (Box 54:, Folder 1194)
    - Combined Financing Program, 1979 (Box 54:, Folder 1195)
  - Department of the Interior, 1979 (Box 54:, Folder 1196)
  - Interstate Commerce Commission, 1979 (Box 54:, Folder 1197)
  - Justice
    - Law Enforcement Assts. Administration, 1979 (Box 55:, Folder 1198)
    - Bureau of Prisons, 1979 (Box 55:, Folder 1199)
    - Immigration and Naturalization, 1979 (Box 55:, Folder 1200)
  - Labor
    - CETA, 1979 (Box 55:, Folder 1201)
    - Hartford CETA, 1979 (Box 55:, Folder 1202)
    - Hartford Consortium CETA Program, 1979 (Box 55:, Folder 1203)
  - National Aeronautics and Science Administration, 1979 (Box 55:, Folder 1204)
  - National Endowment for the Arts, 1979 (Box 55:, Folder 1205)
  - National Endowment for the Humanities, 1979 (Box 55:, Folder 1206)
  - National Labor Relations Board, 1979 (Box 55:, Folder 1207)
  - National Science Foundation, 1979 (Box 55:, Folder 1208)
  - Securities and Exchange Commission, 1979 (Box 55:, Folder 1209)
  - Small Business Administration, 1979 (Box 55:, Folder 1210)
  - State
    - General, 1979 (Box 55:, Folder 1211)
    - Falkovitch, Nyam, 1979 (Box 55:, Folder 1212)
    - Human Rights, 1979 (Box 55:, Folder 1213)
    - Passport and Visa, 1979 (Box 55:, Folder 1214)
  - Transportation
    - Correspondence, 1979 (Box 55:, Folder 1215)
    - Amtrak, 1979 (Box 55:, Folder 1216)
    - Federal Aviation Administration: Controlled Visual Flight Rules, 1979 (Box 55:, Folder 1217)
    - Conrail, 1979 (Box 55:, Folder 1218)
    - I-284, 1979 (Box 55:, Folder 1219)
    - I-291, 1979 (Box 55:, Folder 1220)
  - Treasury
    - Correspondence, 1979 (Box 55:, Folder 1221)
    - IRS, 1979 (Box 55:, Folder 1222)
  - United States Postal Service, 1979 (Box 55:, Folder 1223)
  - U.S. Railroad Retirement Board, 1979 (Box 55:, Folder 1224)
  - Veterans Affairs, 1979 (Box 55:, Folder 1225)
  - Miscellaneous, 1980 (Box 55:, Folder 1226)
  - Agriculture
    - General, 1980 (Box 55:, Folder 1227)
    - Correspondence, 1980 (Box 55:, Folder 1228)
  - Civil Aeronautics Board
    - General, 1980 (Box 55:, Folder 1229)
    - Air New England, 1980 (Box 55:, Folder 1230)
  - Commerce
    - General, 1980 (Box 55:, Folder 1231)
    - Census Bureau, 1980 (Box 55:, Folder 1232)
    - Economic Development Administration, 1980 (Box 55:, Folder 1233)
    - Federal Maritime Administration, 1980 (Box 56:, Folder 1234)
  - Community Services Administration, 1980 (Box 56:, Folder 1235)
  - Defense
    - U.S. Marine Corps, 1980 (Box 56:, Folder 1236)
    - General, 1980 (Box 56:, Folder 1237)
    - Army Corps of Engineers, 1980 (Box 56:, Folder 1238)
    - Navy, 1980 (Box 56:, Folder 1239)
    - Army, 1980 (Box 56:, Folder 1240)
    - Air Force, 1980 (Box 56:, Folder 1241)
  - Department of Energy, 1980 (Box 56:, Folder 1242)
  - Department of Education, 1980 (Box 56:, Folder 1243)
  - Environmental Protection Agency (EPA), 1980 (Box 56:, Folder 1244)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity Commission, 1980 (Box 56:, Folder 1245)
  - Office of the President
    - Wage and Price Stability, 1980 (Box 56:, Folder 1246)
    - Office of Management & Budget, 1980 (Box 56:, Folder 1247)
    - Correspondence, 1980 (Box 56:, Folder 1248)
  - Federal Communications Commission (FCC), 1980 (Box 56:, Folder 1249)
  - Federal Reserve Board, 1980 (Box 56:, Folder 1250)
  - Federal Trade Commission, 1980 (Box 56:, Folder 1251)
  - General Accounting Office (GAO), 1980 (Box 56:, Folder 1252)
  - General Services Administration, 1980 (Box 56:, Folder 1253)
  - Health and Human Services
    - Correspondence, 1980 (Box 56:, Folder 1254)
    - Health, 1980 (Box 56:, Folder 1255)
    - Food and Drug Administration, 1980 (Box 56:, Folder 1256)
    - Welfare, 1980 (Box 56:, Folder 1257)
    - Social Security Administration, 1980 (Box 56:, Folder 1258)
  - Housing and Urban Development
    - Flood Insurance Program, 1980 (Box 56:, Folder 1259)
    - Community Development Block Grants, 1980 (Box 56:, Folder 1260)
  - Department of the Interior, 1980 (Box 56:, Folder 1261)
  - International Trade Commission, 1980 (Box 56:, Folder 1262)
  - Interstate Commerce Commission, 1980 (Box 56:, Folder 1263)
  - Justice
    - Correspondence, 1980 (Box 56:, Folder 1264)
    - Law Enforcement Assts. Administration, 1980 (Box 56:, Folder 1265)
    - Bureau of Prisons, 1980 (Box 56:, Folder 1266)
    - Immigration and Naturalization, 1980 (Box 56:, Folder 1267)
  - Labor
    - Correspondence, 1980 (Box 56:, Folder 1268)
    - CETA, 1980 (Box 56:, Folder 1269)
    - Hartford CETA, 1980 (Box 56:, Folder 1270)
  - National Endowment for the Arts, 1980 (Box 56:, Folder 1271)
  - Office of Personnel Management, 1980 (Box 56:, Folder 1272)
  - United States Postal Service, 1980 (Box 56:, Folder 1273)
  - Securities and Exchange Commission, 1980 (Box 56:, Folder 1274)
  - Small Business Administration, 1980 (Box 56:, Folder 1275)
  - State
    - Human Rights, 1980 (Box 57:, Folder 1276)
    - Passport and Visa, 1980 (Box 57:, Folder 1277)
    - International Whaling Commission, 1980 (Box 57:, Folder 1278)
    - Correspondence, 1980 (Box 57:, Folder 1279)
  - Transportation
    - Federal Aviation Administration, 1980 (Box 57:, Folder 1280)
    - Conrail, 1980 (Box 57:, Folder 1281)
    - Amtrak, 1980 (Box 57:, Folder 1282)
    - US Coast Guard, 1980 (Box 57:, Folder 1283)
    - Poughkeepsie Bridge, 1980 (Box 57:, Folder 1284)
    - Northeast Corridor Improvement, 1980 (Box 57:, Folder 1285)
  - Treasury
    - IRS, 1980 (Box 57:, Folder 1286)
    - General Revenueing Sharing Funds to Cities, 1980 (Box 57:, Folder 1287)
  - U.S. Railroad Retirement Board, 1980 (Box 57:, Folder 1288)
  - Veterans Affairs, 1980 (Box 57:, Folder 1289)
  - Miscellaneous: Consumer Problems, 1981 (Box 57:, Folder 1290)
  - Agriculture
    - General, 1981 (Box 57:, Folder 1291)
    - Farmers Home Administration, 1981 (Box 57:, Folder 1292)
  - Civil Aeronautics Board, 1981 (Box 57:, Folder 1293)
  - Commerce
    - General, 1981 (Box 57:, Folder 1294)
    - Census Bureau, 1981 (Box 57:, Folder 1295)
    - 1980 Census, 1981 (Box 57:, Folder 1296)
  - Defense
    - Army Corps of Engineers, 1981 (Box 57:, Folder 1297)
    - U.S. Marine Corps, 1981 (Box 57:, Folder 1298)
    - Air Force, 1981 (Box 57:, Folder 1299)
    - Army, 1981 (Box 57:, Folder 1300)
    - Navy, 1981 (Box 57:, Folder 1301)
  - Department of Education, 1981 (Box 58:, Folder 1302)
  - Department of Energy, 1981 (Box 58:, Folder 1303)
  - Environmental Protection Agency (EPA)
    - General, 1981 (Box 58:, Folder 1304)
    - Ozone Depleating Chlorofluorocarbons Issue, 1981 (Box 58:, Folder 1305)
  - Office of the President
    - General, 1981 (Box 58:, Folder 1306)
    - Office of Management & Budget, 1981 (Box 58:, Folder 1307)
  - Federal Communications Commission (FCC), 1981 (Box 58:, Folder 1308)
  - Federal Reserve Board, 1981 (Box 58:, Folder 1309)
  - Federal Trade Commission, 1981 (Box 58:, Folder 1310)
  - General Services Administration, 1981 (Box 58:, Folder 1311)
  - Health and Human Services (Formally Health, Education & Welfare)
    - Health, 1981 (Box 58:, Folder 1312)
    - Correspondence, 1981 (Box 58:, Folder 1313)
    - Direct Payment Vendor Issue, 1981 (Box 58:, Folder 1314)
    - Welfare, 1981 (Box 58:, Folder 1315)
    - Food and Drug Administration, 1981 (Box 58:, Folder 1316)
    - Social Security Administration, 1981 (Box 58:, Folder 1317)
  - Housing and Urban Development
    - General, 1981 (Box 58:, Folder 1318)
    - Flood Insurance Program, 1981 (Box 58:, Folder 1319)
  - Department of the Interior, 1981 (Box 58:, Folder 1320)
  - International Trade Commission, 1981 (Box 58:, Folder 1321)
  - Justice
    - General, 1981 (Box 58:, Folder 1322)
    - Bureau of Prisons, 1981 (Box 58:, Folder 1323)
    - Immigration and Naturalization, 1981 (Box 58:, Folder 1324)
  - Labor
    - General, 1981 (Box 58:, Folder 1325)
    - CETA, 1981 (Box 58:, Folder 1326)
  - Office of Personnel Management, 1981 (Box 58:, Folder 1327)
  - Small Business Administration, 1981 (Box 58:, Folder 1328)
  - State
    - Passport and Visa, 1981 (Box 58:, Folder 1329)
    - Human Rights, 1981 (Box 58:, Folder 1330)
  - Transportation, undated
    - Federal Aviation Administration, 1981 (Box 58:, Folder 1331)
    - Amtrak, 1981 (Box 58:, Folder 1332)
    - Conrail, 1981 (Box 58:, Folder 1333)
    - I-84 and I-86 Connector, 1981 (Box 58:, Folder 1334)
  - Treasury: IRS, 1981 (Box 58:, Folder 1335)
  - U.S. Parole Commission, 1981 (Box 58:, Folder 1336)
  - United States Postal Service, 1981 (Box 58:, Folder 1337)
  - Veterans Affairs, 1981 (Box 58:, Folder 1338)
- Series III: Voting Records, 1977-1981
  - Voting Records, 1977-1981 (Box 59:, Folder 1339)
  - Records of Votes, 1971-1975 (Box 112)
  - Voting Record, 92-94 Congress, undated (Box 120)
- Series IV: Bill File, 1973-1980
  - Bill File, 1973-1974 (Box 60:, Folder 1340)
  - Bill File, 1973-1974 (Box 61:, Folder 1341)
  - Bill File, 1975-1976 (Box 61:, Folder 1342)
  - Bill File, 1975-1976 (Box 62:, Folder 1343)
  - Bill File, 1977-1978 (Box 62:, Folder 1344)
  - Bill File, 1977-1978 (Box 63:, Folder 1345)
  - Bill File, 1979-1980 (Box 63:, Folder 1346)
  - Bills introduced, 1971-1972 (Box 124)
  - Bills introduced C - R, undated (Box 139)
  - Bills introduced R - T, undated (Box 128)
  - Bills introduced, U - W, undated (Box 152)
- Series V: Campaign Records, 1970-1976
  - Campaign materials, undated (Box 125)
  - Delegate lists, Campaign finances, undated (Box 130)
  - Campaign Records, 1970 (Box 64:, Folder 1347)
  - Campaign Records, 1972 (Box 64:, Folder 1348)
  - Campaign Records, 1972 (Box 145)
  - Campaign materials, 1974 (Box 127)
  - Campaign materials, 1976 (Box 126)
  - Campaign materials, Camapign Adv. Regulators, 1976 (Box 129)
  - Campaign materials, 1976 (Box 144)
  - Campaign materials, 1976 (Box 148)
  - Campaign poster, undated (Box OS)
- Series VI: Press Releases, 1975-1980
  - Press releases, 1971 (Box 133)
  - Press releases, 1971-1974 (Box 131)
  - Press releases, 1973 (Box 151)
  - Press releases, 1973-1974 (Box 143)
  - Press releases, 1974-1976 (Box 117)
  - Press Releases, 1975-1977 July (Box 65:, Folder 1349)
  - Press Releases, 1977 August - 1980 June (Box 66:, Folder 1350)
  - Press releases, 1977-1978 (Box 121)
  - Press releases, 1979-1980 (Box 134)
  - Press releases, 1980-1981 (Box 113)
- Series VII: Meeting Notices and Schedules, 1971-1978
  - Meeting Notices and Schedules, 1971-1978 (Box 67:, Folder 1351)
  - Meeting Notices and Schedules, 1978 (Box 68:, Folder 1352)
- Series VIII: Questionnaire Replies, 1974, 1975
  - Questionnaire Replies, 1974 (Box 68:, Folder 1353)
  - Questionnaire Replies D-L, 1975 (Box 69:, Folder 1354)
  - Questionnaire Replies C-W, 1975 (Box 70:, Folder 1355)
- Series IX: State and Town Files, undated, 1971-1978
  - State and Town Files, undated (Box 71:, Folder 1356)
  - State and Town Files: Berlin-Glastonbury, 1971-1976 (Box 72:, Folder 1357)
  - State and Town Files: Hartford, 1971-1976 (Box 73:, Folder 1358)
  - State and Town Files: Hebron-Windsor, 1971-1976 (Box 74:, Folder 1359)
  - State and Town Files, 1977-1978 (Box 75:, Folder 1360)
- Series X: Grant Files, 1977-1981
  - Grant Files, 1977-1981 (Box 76:, Folder 1361)
  - Grant Files, 1977-1981 (Box 77:, Folder 1362)
- Series XI: Project Files, undated, 1971-1981
  - Food, undated (Box 78:, Folder 1363)
  - Senior Citizens, undated (Box 78:, Folder 1364)
  - Economic Reconversion, undated (Box 78:, Folder 1365)
  - Food, undated (Box 79:, Folder 1366)
  - Railroads, undated (Box 79:, Folder 1367)
  - Space Shuttle, undated (Box 80:, Folder 1368)
  - Lockheed, undated (Box 81:, Folder 1369)
  - Health, undated (Box 81:, Folder 1370)
  - I-291, undated (Box 82:, Folder 1371)
  - Colt, undated (Box 82:, Folder 1372)
  - Lumber, undated (Box 82:, Folder 1373)
  - Energy, undated (Box 82:, Folder 1374)
  - U.A.C., undated (Box 83:, Folder 1375)
  - Energy, undated (Box 83:, Folder 1376)
  - I-291, undated (Box 83:, Folder 1377)
  - Health, undated (Box 84:, Folder 1378)
  - Education, undated (Box 84:, Folder 1379)
  - Park River, undated (Box 84:, Folder 1380)
  - Various, undated (Box 85:, Folder 1381)
- Series XII: Personal Correspondence, 1971-1979
  - Personal Correspondence, 1971-1973 (Box 86:, Folder 1382)
  - Personal Correspondence, 1971-1973 (Box 87:, Folder 1383)
  - Personal Correspondence, 1978-1979 (Box 88:, Folder 1384)
- Series XIII: Redistricting Materials, 1970-1973
  - Redistricting Materials, 1970-1973 (Box 88:, Folder 1385)
- Series XIV: Office Management Files, 1971-1979
  - Office Management Files, 1971-1973 (Box 89:, Folder 1386)
  - Office Management Files, 1974-1977 (Box 90:, Folder 1387)
  - Office Management Files, 1978-1979 (Box 91:, Folder 1388)
- Series XV: Speech Files, 1970-1980
  - Speech Files, 1970-1980 (Box 92:, Folder 1389)
  - Speaking Engagements, 1971-1972 (Box 135)
  - Speaking Engagements, 1973-1976 (Box 138)
  - Speaking Engagements, 1976-1977 (Box 138)
  - Speaking Engagements, 1977-1980 (Box 146)
- Series XVI: Topic Files, undated, 1972-1980
  - Aged, undated (Box 93:, Folder 1390)
  - Army Corps of Engineers, undated (Box 93:, Folder 1391)
  - Anthony, Susan B., undated (Box 93:, Folder 1392)
  - Asbestos, undated (Box 93:, Folder 1393)
  - Blind, undated (Box 93:, Folder 1394)
  - Blomberg, Arthur, undated (Box 93:, Folder 1395)
  - Budget, undated (Box 93:, Folder 1396)
  - CRCOG, undated (Box 93:, Folder 1397)
  - Career, undated (Box 93:, Folder 1398)
  - Census 1980, undated (Box 93:, Folder 1399)
  - Civic Center, undated (Box 93:, Folder 1400)
  - Clean Air Act, undated (Box 93:, Folder 1401)
  - Commerce, undated (Box 93:, Folder 1402)
  - Community Development, undated (Box 94:, Folder 1403-1404)
  - Congressional, undated (Box 94:, Folder 1405)
  - Congressional Research Services, undated (Box 94:, Folder 1406)
  - Congress Watch, undated (Box 94:, Folder 1407)
  - Consumer Price Index, undated (Box 94:, Folder 1408)
  - Community Renewal Team, undated (Box 94:, Folder 1409)
  - Connecticut
    - Public Expenditure Council, undated (Box 94:, Folder 1410)
    - General, undated (Box 94:, Folder 1411)
    - Humanities, undated (Box 94:, Folder 1412)
    - Housing and Finance Authority, undated (Box 94:, Folder 1413)
    - River Committee, undated (Box 94:, Folder 1414)
    - Public Expenditure Council, undated (Box 94:, Folder 1415)
    - CSEA, undated (Box 94:, Folder 1416)
  - Contributions, undated (Box 94:, Folder 1417)
  - Cotter Bills, undated (Box 94:, Folder 1418)
  - Cotter Plans, undated (Box 94:, Folder 1419)
  - Cuba, undated (Box 94:, Folder 1420)
  - Directory, undated (Box 94:, Folder 1421)
  - Economic Development Act, undated (Box 94:, Folder 1422)
  - EDA, undated (Box 94:, Folder 1423)
  - Education, undated (Box 94:, Folder 1424)
  - Election, undated (Box 94:, Folder 1425)
  - Environmental Protection Agency (EPA), undated (Box 94:, Folder 1426)
  - Enterprise Zone, undated (Box 94:, Folder 1427)
  - Farmers Home Administration, undated (Box 94:, Folder 1428)
  - Fire Departments, undated (Box 94:, Folder 1429)
  - Flags, undated (Box 94:, Folder 1430)
  - GAD, undated (Box 95:, Folder 1431)
  - Governor, undated (Box 95:, Folder 1432)
  - Grants, undated (Box 95:, Folder 1433)
  - Hazardous Waste, undated (Box 95:, Folder 1434)
  - Health Care, undated (Box 95:, Folder 1435)
  - HGOCO, undated (Box 95:, Folder 1435)
  - Housing, undated (Box 95:, Folder 1437)
  - Housing and Urban Development (HUD), undated (Box 95:, Folder 1438)
  - Insulation, undated (Box 95:, Folder 1439)
  - Intern, undated (Box 95:, Folder 1440)
  - Issue files, undated (Box 114)
  - Library of Congress, undated (Box 95:, Folder 1441)
  - MX Missle, undated (Box 96:, Folder 1442)
  - Medicare Forum, undated (Box 96:, Folder 1443)
  - Bloomfield Medicare, undated (Box 96:, Folder 1444)
  - Methadone Clinic, undated (Box 96:, Folder 1445)
  - Oil, undated (Box 96:, Folder 1446)
  - Park River, undated (Box 96:, Folder 1447)
  - PCBs, undated (Box 96:, Folder 1448)
  - Press, undated (Box 96:, Folder 1449)
  - Railroads, undated (Box 97:, Folder 1450)
  - Reagan's Economic Plan, undated (Box 97:, Folder 1451)
  - Reappointment, undated (Box 97:, Folder 1452)
  - Rep Living, undated (Box 97:, Folder 1453)
  - Revenue Sharing, undated (Box 97:, Folder 1454)
  - Regional Support Group, undated (Box 97:, Folder 1455)
  - Rodent Control, undated (Box 97:, Folder 1456)
  - Social Security, undated (Box 97:, Folder 1457)
  - STIP, undated (Box 97:, Folder 1458)
  - Student Assistance, undated (Box 97:, Folder 1459)
  - TeleLecture, undated (Box 97:, Folder 1460)
  - Trinity, undated (Box 97:, Folder 1461)
  - UMTA, undated (Box 97:, Folder 1462)
  - Unemployment Tax, undated (Box 97:, Folder 1463)
  - UT, undated (Box 97:, Folder 1464)
  - Unity Contractors, undated (Box 97:, Folder 1465)
  - Urban Parks, undated (Box 97:, Folder 1466)
  - Water, undated (Box 97:, Folder 1467)
  - West Indian Week, undated (Box 97:, Folder 1468)
  - White House, undated (Box 97:, Folder 1469)
  - Wife Abuse, undated (Box 97:, Folder 1470)
  - Windfall Profits Tax, undated (Box 98:, Folder 1471)
  - Connecticut
    - Congressional Convention, undated (Box 98:, Folder 1472)
    - Campaign
      - Radio, undated (Box 98:, Folder 1473)
      - News Clippings, undated (Box 98:, Folder 1474)
      - Corrdinators, undated (Box 98:, Folder 1475)
      - TV, undated (Box 98:, Folder 1476)
    - Endorsements, undated (Box 98:, Folder 1477)
    - Campaign
      - Press Releases, undated (Box 98:, Folder 1478)
      - Lowengard Material, undated (Box 98:, Folder 1479)
      - Meeting Notes, undated (Box 98:, Folder 1480)
  - Grant Project, undated (Box 98:, Folder 1481)
  - Campaign, 1980 (Box 98:, Folder 1482)
  - Funeral, undated (Box 98:, Folder 1483)
  - Campaign, Print, undated (Box 98:, Folder 1484)
  - Election Stats, 1978 (Box 98:, Folder 1485)
  - Coordinators, 1974 (Box 98:, Folder 1486)
  - Campaign Budget, undated (Box 98:, Folder 1487)
  - Grant Awards, undated (Box 98:, Folder 1488)
  - Issue Letters by Town: Berlin-Windsor, 1977-1981 (Box 99:, Folder 1489)
  - Issue and Policy Letters: District Office, 1977-1981 (Box 100:, Folder 1490)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1972-1974 (Box 101:, Folder 1491)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1975, 1977, 1978 (Box 102:, Folder 1492)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1976, 1979 (Box 103:, Folder 1493)
  - Press Release Files, 1972-1975 (Box 104:, Folder 1494)
  - Press Release Files, 1976-1979 (Box 105:, Folder 1495)
  - Press Release Files, 1980 (Box 106:, Folder 1496)
  - Press Release Files, 1980-1981 (Box 107:, Folder 1497)
  - Congressional Campaign Files, 1972-1978 (Box 108:, Folder 1498)
  - Congressional Issues and Publications, undated (Box 109:, Folder 1499)
- Series XVII: Audiovisual materials, undated
  - Audio, cassettes (6) and reel-to-reel (14), undated (Box 110)
  - Video, film and audio, undated (Box 116)
  - Audio cassette, undated (Box 118)
  - Photographs, undated (Box 119)
- series XVIII: Unsorted materials, undated, 1970-1981
  - Scrapbooks, 1970-1972 (Box 111)
  - Scrapbooks, 1973-1980 (Box 115)
  - Correspondence, directories, clippings, undated (Box 118)
  - Scrapbooks (2 loose), undated
  - Congressional appointments, plaques, undated (Box 122)
  - Expenses, receipts, 1979-1981 (Box 123)
  - Congressional Record reprints
    - 1973-1975 (Box 136)
    - 1975-1976 (Box 141)
    - 1971-1973 (Box 142)
    - 1977-1978 (Box 149)
    - 1978-1981 (Box 150)
  - Correspondence, appointments, testaments, undated (Box 137)
  - Expense receipts, 1978 (Box 147)